A train is arriving.
Please step back.
電車が参ります　お下がりください
Train A1971 is suddenly accelerating.
It's out of control.
走行中のＡ１９７１が急激に加速
コントロールできません
A runaway train...?
暴走？
As it stands,
このままでは　数分で前を走る列車と衝突します
it's going to crash into the train
ahead of it within a few minutes.
Evacuate all in service trains immediately!
全ての運行列車を緊急待避
Hurry up and evacuate
all the passengers!
乗客の避難誘導を急げ
All the trains have been brought
to the evacuation section.
各列車を待避区画へ誘導
Okay, now, switch
the tracks back.
よし　ポイントを戻せ
It's rejecting the signal.
信号　受け付けません
なっ…
Wha...
A1971 is headed
to the evacuation section?
Ａ１９７１が　待避区画に？
Let's get started.
始めよう
車両点検のため　しばらく　停車いたします
We're stopping momentarily
for a car inspection.
We're sorry for the inconvenience.
Please stand by and remain in the train.
誠に申し訳ありませんが　そのまま　車内でお待ちください
「デコンポーザー　対象を完全排除します」
Decomposer.
Target will be completely eliminated.
The wastewater facility
in the underground area
列車が待避中の地下エリアで　排水施設が破壊された
where the trains are taking shelter
has been destroyed.
They led all the trains to one place
by making one train go out of control
暴走させ　全列車を誘導
隣接エリアの汚染水を利用し　孤立させた
and isolated them using wastewater
from the neighboring area.
シェルターのおかげで　水没は免れているが…
Fortunately, the shelter is keeping them
from being submerged, but...
Because they can't drain the water,
the passengers are stuck there.
排水できない以上　乗客の脱出は不可能よ
Kamui and his group have
confined themselves there as well.
自分たちごと閉じ込めた…
What's the purpose of that?
その狙いは何だ？
We've taken too much
backbone out of the MLIT.
国交省を骨抜きにし過ぎたわね
To think that they still haven't
been able to drain the wastewater...
鉄道の隣接エリアが浸水したままとは…
I see...
そう…
So we kept proof of the scandal
in case they try to take our place again?
彼らが再び私たちに取って代わろうとしたときのために
不祥事のネタを残していたわけね
Thanks to that,
おかげで　乗客５００人余りが　鹿矛囲の人質になったようよ
it looks like over five hundred passengers
became Kamui's hostages.
His goal?
目的？
No. If all he wanted was
to reproduce the Season of Hell,
まさか
地獄の季節の再現だけで　満足する程度なら
we would've been able
to take care of him by now.
とっくに処分できているわ
この人数　三係だけじゃ処理できないぞ
Division 3 alone isn't enough
to deal with all of them.
Where do you think
you're going?
どこへ行こうというのです？
This is an emergency.
緊急事態です
We need to analyze the situation
and come up with a plan right away.
即時　状況の分析　作戦の立案を
From the moment a member
of your family became a hostage,
あなたはこの事件に関わることはできない
you became unable
to participate in this investigation.
肉親が人質になった時点で
That's my decision to make.
I'm the Inspector here.
それを判断するのは監視官である　私です
But this is Chief Kasei's decision.
これは禾生局長のお考えです
Please... move away.
そこを…　どいてください
I'm not at fault. I'm not at fault.
I'm not at fault. I'm not...
私は悪くない　私は悪くない　私は悪くない　私は…
That's right...
そうだ
Feel the pain that comes from being
the reason someone precious to you died.
自分のせいで　大切な存在が失われる　苦しみを味わえ
Paint yourself black,
Akane Tsunemori.
黒く染まれ　常守朱
奪われ続けるなら
If I keep having things taken away from me, I'm gonna lose my mind
Ubaware tsuzukeru nara mou kurutte shimau yo
奪われ続けるなら
もう狂ってしまうよ
This endless "end" will make me stop breathing
Owari no nai "owari" ni boku wa iki wo shinaku natte
終わりの無い「終わり」に僕は息をしなくなって
Enigmatic Feeling
Enigmatic feeling
Why do they have to take things away from me? I'm about to fall apart
Ubawanakya ikenai no? Mou hodokete shimau yo
奪わなきゃいけないの
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
The world began to melt
Sekai ga tokedashite
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
God descended to confront and ask me
Kami-sama ga orite kite boku ni tsukitsuketa
神様が降りて来て
僕に突きつけた
"Who are you?"
Who are you?
I freed myself by walking in the divide of this world broken into two
Futatsu ni wakareta sekai ni sotte jibun wo hanatta
２つに分かれた世界に沿って
自分を放った
Is there only one God in such a fine borderline?
Kamihitoe darou kamihitoe darou kyoukaisen kami wa hitori na no?
紙一重だろう　紙一重だろう
境界線　神は１人なの
I'm gonna lose my mind, I'm gonna lose my mind...
Okashiku natte okashiku natte
おかしくなって おかしくなって
Suddenly I'll find myself taking you away
Fui ni kimi wo ubatte shimau no darou
ふいに君を奪ってしまうのだろう
Crazy! Crazy!
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
Because my heart can't focus
Pinto no awanai kokoro ni
ピントの合わない心に
Shake me! Shake me!
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I can't even look into the mirror
Kagami sae mo nozokenai
鏡さえも覗けない
Crime Coefficient is 148.
She is a target for enforcement action.
「犯罪係数　１４８」
「執行対象です」
#10: Gauging the Soul
Start with those who're likely to go over 300.
Knock them out using Paralyzer.
３００を超えそうな者から　パラライザーで意識を奪え
They're randomly
shooting passengers?!
乗客へ無差別に発砲？
How terrible...
何てことを…
I'm counting on you since the Chief
has ordered Akane on standby.
頼んだわよ
朱ちゃんが局長命令で待機扱いなんだから
Right, I'm the only one they've got.
I'm the top of Division 1 now.
そう　私しかいないんだ
私が　一係のトップなんだ
It's okay. I simply acted
according to Sibyl's will.
大丈夫　私はシビュラの意思に従っただけ
There's no way
my Psycho-Pass will get clouded.
サイコパスが濁るわけない
D-Dominators don't work on Kamui.
H-How are we going to...
か…鹿矛囲って　ドミネーター　効かないのに
ど…どうやって…
Even so, we cannot just sit back
and let this happen, right?
だからって　出動しないわけには　いかないでしょ
I wish we at least knew
what his goal is...
せめて　鹿矛囲の目的が分かればな
Kamui's goal is to retaliate
against the Togane Foundation.
鹿矛囲の目的は東金財団への報復です
This incident should be
connected to that in some way, too.
今回も何らかの形でつながっているはずです
It's true that both Kitazawa's crime
and the barricade incident
確かに　喜汰沢の事件も　立てこもり施設も
are connected
to the Togane Foundation.
東金財団につながる
But on what grounds
are you saying it's retaliation?
でも　それを報復だとする根拠は？
This.
これです
It was the Togane Foundation
who pushed for Kamui's surgery.
東金財団が鹿矛囲の手術を推進しました
Misako Togane
They used him in a clinical trial
for the benefit of the Foundation.
財団の利益のため　臨床実験に利用したんです
Surgery... A multi-body
brain transplant...
手術…　脳の多体移植
From that reason,
I guessed that
その経緯から　鹿矛囲は東金財団に恨みを抱いたと推測しました
Kamui had come to hold a grudge
against the Togane Foundation.
It's flying back and forth.
飛んでる　飛んでる
With this much data
flying around...
これだけ飛ばせば…
This is... I suspected that
might be what they were up to.
これは…　やはり　そうきたわね
A ruling is handed down
without fail based on the crime,
ドミネーターが捉えた情報によって
using the information
captured by the Dominators.
罪に応じた裁定が　必ず下される
これだけ　絶え間なく　一挙に動作すれば
If so many are being used
at the same time like this,
the amount of data
becomes massive,
データは膨大となり
which should overload
the normal processing routes.
通常の処理では追い付かなくなるはず
When that happens, a bypass route
appears on the network for them to use.
そうなったとき　使用されるのがネットワークに現れるバイパス経路
The security on the backup data channels
isn't as good.
バックアップのデータ経路はセキュリティーが一段劣る
So they wanted
to trigger its use, huh...
それを使わせるのが　目的というわけね
We've located the bypass.
This may actually work.
バイパスつかみました　これなら何とか
Keep working on it.
そのまま続けてくれ
You gathered Dominators in order to find
the location of the Sibyl System.
ドミネーターを集めていたのは　シビュラシステムの位置を探るため
Isn't that right, Kirito?
そうなのね　桐斗君
I thought I ordered you
to stay on standby.
君には　待機を命じたはずだが？
I don't think we can afford
to stand idly by in this situation.
そんな　悠長なことを　言っている状況ではないはずよ
I see, then I'll assign you
a different task.
そうか　ならば　別の任務を与えるとしよう
Assassinating Kamui...
鹿矛囲桐斗の暗殺
That's right.
そのとおりだ
I knew it.
やはり　そう
What?
何？
Considering the nature
of the crimes he committed so far
今までに起こした事件の性質や
and his connection
to the Season of Hell,
地獄の季節という接点を考慮すれば
it's obvious that
the Togane Foundation isn't his target.
鹿矛囲の目的が　東金財団ではないことは明白
What he's questioning
is the color...
彼が問うているのは色
...and the one he's asking
that question to is Sibyl.
その相手はシビュラ
You're in a hurry
to eliminate Kamui
鹿矛囲の始末を急ぐのは
because he's about
to come in contact with Sibyl.
今まさに　彼がシビュラに触れようとしているから
You do like to stick your nose
where it doesn't belong, don't you?
相変わらず　余計なことを考えるのが好きだな
As it stands, he'll probably achieve
his goal within an hour, as you've guessed.
君の推測どおり　このままいけば
あと１時間もしないうちに　やつは目的を果たすことだろう
Of course, I don't intend
to let that happen.
むろん　そんなことを許すつもりはない
I ordered Division 3, who was
first on the scene, to place bombs
現場に先行した三係には　犯人が立てこもっている
right above the area
the culprits are occupying.
区画の頭上に爆弾を設置するよう指示してある
What're you thinking?!
There are over five hundred hostages there!
何を考えているの
あそこには　５００人以上の　人質がいるのよ
It's very unlikely for humans
to keep their Psycho-Pass clear
閉鎖空間で　一方的に　狩られる側となった人間が
サイコパスをクリアに保てる可能性は極めて低い
when they become hunted
one-sidedly in a closed space.
Most of them are probably
latent criminals by now.
すでに　ほとんどが潜在犯だろう
That cannot be a reason
for us to simply let them die!
だからって　見殺しにしていいわけがない
This is an absurd operation!
こんな　ふざけた作戦
It's not open for discussion.
And it is also your duty.
決定事項なのだよ
そして　君の任務でもある
Take command of the detonation.
Finish it with your own hands.
起爆の指揮を執れ
君の手で終わらせろ
What a transparent lie.
You just want to kill Kamui, don't you?
しらじらしい…　鹿矛囲を殺したいだけでしょう
This is in order to protect
the society and Sibyl.
社会とシビュラを守るためだ
Unless we stop Kamui's
attempts to destroy order,
鹿矛囲による秩序崩壊を止めねば　はるかに多くの犠牲が出る
many more people
are going to die.
Also... I received an unfortunate report
just a moment ago.
それと…　今しがた　残念な知らせを受けてね
Your grandmother Aoi Tsunemori's body
was found in the warehouse district.
君の祖母　常守葵の遺体が倉庫街で発見された
It looks like she was restrained
and beaten to death.
拘束された状態で　撲殺されたようだ
It's a cruel crime.
むごたらしい犯行だよ
I'll entrust the last trigger with you.
最後の引き金は　君に委ねよう
Protect this society
we all live in.
われわれの住む　この社会を守りたまえ
I have faith in you,
Inspector Tsunemori.
信頼しているよ　常守監視官
Kill Kamui, Akane Tsunemori.
鹿矛囲を殺せ　常守朱
Realize how powerless you are.
己の無力さを思い知れ
Give in to the desire to kill,
and get your own self back.
自分を取り戻すための殺意を肯定しろ
Then you'll paint
yourself black without fail.
そうすれば　必ず黒く染まる
Are you going to kill him?
殺すのか？　やつを
爆破？　それに東金財団の関連施設は警戒の必要なしって…
Blow up the whole area?!
And there's no need to watch facilities
connected to the Togane Foundation?
そんな命令　私　聞いてません
I was not informed
of those orders.
こちらを最優先だ　一係は指示があるまで待機を
This is our main priority.
Have your Division stand by until further instructed.
Why...?
そんな…
一刻を争う状況だというのに　どうなってるんだ
This is a very time-sensitive situation.
What's going on?
I don't know...
but maybe I should.
分かりません…　でも　そうすべきなのかも
It's not like you.
Remember, you said,
らしくないな
あんた　言ったよな
「法が人を守るんじゃない　人が法を守るんだ」って
"The law doesn't protect people.
People protect the law."
Wasn't the reason you tried to stop me
because you believed in that?
それを信じてるから　あんたは俺を止めようとしたんじゃないのか？
Yes, it was... at the time.
そうでした…　あのときは
Well, I guess I don't have
any right to say that.
まっ　俺が言えた義理じゃないか
Sibyl cannot judge Kamui,
but we have to stop him.
シビュラに鹿矛囲は裁けない
でも　鹿矛囲を止めなくちゃいけない
There's no other option left.
もう　手段がないんです
違うな
You're wrong.
It's not that there's no other option left.
もう　手段がないんじゃない
今は　手段がないだけだ
It's just that no options
are presenting themselves right now.
可能性のピースはもう揃ってるはずだ
You should already have
all the pieces you need.
あんたが　ためらっているだけで
You're just hesitating.
I cannot fail... but...
失敗は　許されない　でも…
Isn't it worth taking a chance?
賭けてみても　いいんじゃないか
負けるなよ
Don't let them win.
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
お前…
What're you...
Koichi Kuwashima...
I have a favor to ask.
桒島浩一　あなたに頼みがある
Is this Kirito Kamui?
鹿矛囲桐斗ね
I'm Akane Tsunemori
from the CID Division 1, MWPSB.
私は　公安局刑事課一係所属　常守朱
How's Koichi doing?
浩一は　どうしてるかな？
He became cooperative
after I talked to him.
私の話を聞いて協力的になってくれたわ
Sibyl is trying to bury you
along with the passengers.
シビュラは　乗客ごと　あなたを葬る気よ
その前に　出口は　見つかる
We'll find the exit
before that happens.
その場合
In that case, all the Inspectors
and Enforcers will stand in your way.
全ての監視官および執行官があなたの前に立ちふさがるでしょうね
You think I'd be afraid of that?
僕が　それを恐れるとでも？
Kirito Kamui, if you release
the hostages, I'll grant your wish.
鹿矛囲桐斗　人質を解放するなら
私が　あなたの望みをかなえる
地下のマップデータを送ったわ
I've sent you a map
of the underground.
目印の地点まで来なさい　そこで…
Come to the point marked.
There, I'll...
何を考えている？
What are you thinking?
The Omnipotence Paradox...
全能者のパラドクス
鹿矛囲の目的はシビュラシステムを裁くこと
Kamui's goal is to judge
the Sibyl System.
You guys should accept that.
あなたたちは　それを受け入れるべきよ
That will result in you
judging him as well.
それが　鹿矛囲を裁くことにも　つながる
You've been perfecting
your judgments
あなたたちは免罪体質者という裁くことができない例外を取り込むことで
by taking in criminally asymptomatic people,
the ones you cannot judge.
完全な裁きを実現させてきた
However, a new exception
has appeared.
しかし　新たな例外が生まれた
個人ではなく　集合体として　形をなす鹿矛囲
Kamui exists as a collective entity,
not as an individual.
In order to judge him,
there's no other choice but for Sibyl to accept
彼を裁くには　彼を成り立たせている概念をシビュラが認める他ない
the concept that makes him valid.
君は何を口にしているのか分かっていない
You don't know
what you're talking about.
To judge him, we need to measure
his Psycho-Pass as a collective entity.
あれを裁くには　集合体としてのサイコパスを計測する必要がある
だが　そうなれば…
But if that happens...
Sibyl, which is also a collective entity,
becomes a target for judgment as well.
集合体であるシビュラも　裁きの対象になる
それが　彼の狙いだった
That was his goal.
自ら社会の脅威となることで
By turning himself
into a threat to society,
he creates a situation
where you have no choice
集合的サイコパスを認めざるを得ない状況をつくり
but to accept
a collective Psycho-Pass,
which then creates a paradox.
And then after all that, he judges you.
あなたたちをパラドクスに追い込んだ上で　裁く
That's all the more reason why
we can't allow him to get closer to Sibyl.
ならば　余計に　やつを　シビュラに近づけるわけにはいくまい
And you kill him without judging him?
By denying your own perfection?
そして　裁くことなく　彼を処分するの？
自らの完全性を否定して
You're so focused
on the immediate objective
君は目先の目的にとらわれ　事の重大さを理解してない
and have lost sight
of the bigger picture...
...which is the impact on society
once it accepts a collective Psycho-Pass...
集合的サイコパスを認めた社会が　どのようなものになるかを
A society in which people
are possibly judged as a group
個人個人がクリアでも
集団として　裁かれる可能性がある社会
even though
each individual is clear...
I do understand its risk.
そのリスクは　理解しているわ
But if you confront the problem
you've been avoiding,
でも　今まで目を背けていた　その問題を直視することは
it should lead you
to evolve as well.
あなたたちの進化にも　つながるはず
On the contrary,
if you avoid this problem
逆に　この問題から目を背け
and choose the easy way out by killing Kamui,
there's no future for you guys.
鹿矛囲の処分という逃避を選ぶなら
あなたたちに未来はない
I'm tired of listening
to your pompous talk.
君のご託は　聞き飽きた
独走する気なら　君の監視官権限を剥奪する
If you're going to act on your own,
I'll rescind your rights as an Inspector.
We'll have to think about eliminating you
from this society as well.
君をこの社会から抹消することも考えねばな
I'm saying your individual opinion
doesn't matter, Misako Togane!
あなた個人の見解は　どうでもいいと言っているの
東金美沙子
Sibyl System...
シビュラシステム
The reason you guys are allowed
to exist in this society
あなたたちが　この社会に　存在を許されている理由は
is that you can cast an equal
and perfect judgment.
平等で　完璧な裁きを　行えるからよ
Now that there is an error
in that perfection,
その完全性に　ほころびが生まれた今
you can say that the value
of your existence itself is shaken.
あなたたちの存在価値　そのものが揺らいでいるといっていい
You don't know
what you're saying.
知ったふうな口を…
What you need to do to continue
serving a purpose in this society...
あなたたちが　この社会に必要であり続けるため
何を選択するべきか
Think over that
carefully as a group.
全員で　じっくり考えることね
Are you really sure about this?
本当に　よろしいのですね？
Yes, do it.
構わん　やりたまえ
Roger!
了解
會川の敵だ　死ね
This is to avenge Aikawa...!
Die!
What's going on?
They aren't detonating.
どういうことだ？　起爆しない
公安に爆薬なんて配備されない以上
Because the MWPSB isn't provided
with explosives, if you want to use them,
使うとなれば　事件を通じて手に入れた物を流用するしかない
you have no choice but to use
what you obtained through crimes.
この数カ月で　爆弾が絡んだ事件は一つだけ
And there was only one incident
that involved bombs in the past few months.
Kitazawa's bombs were made so
that we can override and control them.
喜汰沢の爆弾は
こちらで優先的にコントロールできるようにしてあるの
Isn't that wonderful?
Kamui can see through everything.
ねっ　すてきでしょ？
こんなふうに　何もかも見通せるからこそ
That's exactly why
he can make everyone clear.
鹿矛囲は　みんなをクリアにしてあげられるのよ
あとは　公安を　ここに縛り付けておくだけ
All we need to do now
is keep the MWPSB here.
もう少しで　鹿矛囲が　世界をクリアにしてくれる
Kamui will make
the world clear before long.
Draining Water
水位が下がった　別の排水施設を利用したんだわ
The water level has fallen!
They must've used a different wastewater facility.
人質が解放された？
The hostages
have been released?!
Roger that. We'll head there
immediately to capture the culprits.
分かった　直ちに犯人グループの確保に向かう
Inspector Shimotsuki!
霜月監視官
This can't be... No...
そんな…　違う…
Victim: Aoi Tsunemori
Death from hemorrhagic shock resulting
from external injuries caused by physical trauma
It's not my fault...
It's not...!
私のせいじゃない…　こんなの…
Inspector, what're you doing?!
監視官　何をしている
あ…　あれ？
Hm?
What's the matter?
どうしたの？
Wh-Where's Enforcer Togane?
と…　東金執行官は？
監視官
Inspector.
禾生局長から　あなたが　ここに来ることを聞きました
Chief Kasei told me
that you'd be here.
Please let me come with you.
俺も同行させてください
なぜ
Why?
You must already know the connection
between Misako Togane and Kamui.
もう気付いているはずです　東金美沙子と鹿矛囲の関係を
俺の母が　あの怪物を生み出した
My mother created that monster.
その責任は息子の俺が負わねばならない
The responsibility for correcting that
falls to me, her son,
even if I may end up having
to stain my hands with blood.
たとえ　この手を　血で汚すことになっても…
殺すつもりですか　鹿矛囲を
Are you going to kill Kamui?
If it was Enforcer Kogami,
he would've done so.
狡噛執行官なら　そうしたはずだ
行きましょう　監視官
Let's go, Inspector.
Why don't you stop
acting, Mr. Togane?
お芝居は　もう　やめませんか　東金さん
あなたの母親が　鹿矛囲に行った　脳の多体移植
The multi-body brain transplant
your mother had performed on Kamui...
I know a system
very similar to that.
私は　それに　よく似た　システムを知っている
もちろん　彼女も　知っていたことになる
Which means she, of course,
knew about it, too.
But that is not allowed
in this society...
でも　この社会で　それは　許されないこと
Misako Togane
免罪体質者を除いて
...except for those
who are criminally asymptomatic.
If Misako Togane
was criminally asymptomatic,
東金美沙子が　免罪体質者なら
she must've been
taken in by the system.
システムに組み込まれているはず
And, it's highly likely that she's forced
to be in charge of this whole matter.
そして　今回の件で
責任者として　活動を　強いられている可能性が高い
In other words, the one who's acting
as Chief Kasei right now is Misako Togane.
つまり　今　禾生局長の皮をかぶっているのは
東金美沙子
監視官　俺には　何の話か　さっぱり…
Inspector, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I saw your background data...
the real data that has been hidden.
あなたの経歴データを　見せてもらいました
隠匿していた　本当のデータを
Name: Sakuya Togane
Affiliation: CID Division 1, MWPSB
Occupation: Enforcer
Date of Birth: June 6, 2086
Age: 28
Blood Type: AB
きっかけは　霜月監視官の報告書です
It all started with
Inspector Shimotsuki's report.
Name: Sakuya Togane
Affiliation: CID Division 1, MWPSB
Occupation: Enforcer
Date of Birth: June 6, 2073
Age: 41
Blood Type: AB
あなたの経歴と　矛盾する内容が多々あった
Many parts of it were
inconsistent with your background.
So I reexamined your file.
それで　ファイルを調べ直したんです
なるほど
I see...
You drove all the Inspectors
into becoming latent criminals.
監視官を　ことごとく　潜在犯に陥れてきた　その経歴
To tell you the truth,
I didn't want to believe it.
正直　信じたくなかった
Or, I wanted to think that
you weren't doing it intentionally.
もしくは意図してやっているわけではないと思いたかった
Like Mr. Saiga?
雑賀先生のように？
But you were different.
でも　あなたは違った
If I look back at what you said
and how you behaved, it gradually becomes clear
今までの　あなたの言動を振り返れば
だんだんと分かってくる
what you wanted to do.
あなたが　どうしたかったのか
私を黒く染めたかった　そうですね？
You wanted to paint me black.
Isn't that right?
Someone like you
can't color her.
彼女は君程度には染められないよ
鹿矛囲桐斗…
Kirito Kamui...!
好都合だ
This is perfect.
貴様の存在が　母さんを　おとしめる
Your existence
demeans my mother. So...
だから…
「犯罪係数　７６９　リーサル・エリミネーター」
Crime Coefficient is 769.
Lethal Eliminator.
貴様は　存在してはならない
...you cannot exist!
All is calm All is bright
All is calm, all is bright
Don't!
駄目
Be gone, you pitch-black soul.
散れ　漆黒
A whispering fallen angel
Sasayaku tenshi wa ochite
囁く天使は堕ちて
優しく食むわ　あなたの全てを
Gently devours you, body and soul
Yasashiku hamu wa anata no subete o
It's my guilty
気づく　目を見開いてる
You notice me
Kidzuku
With your eyes wide open,
Me o mihiraiteru
仄青い混凝土
A faint blue as lifeless as concrete
Honoaoi konkuriito
In a cold tone,
Tsumetaku watashi o
冷たく私を
Call my name and give me a kiss
そして抱きしめて
And then hold me in the arms of the empty shell that is your body
Soshite dakishimete anata no inai sono karada de
あなたのいないその体で
吐き出しその生命は
That soul that you've cast out
Hakidashita sono inochi wa
まだ形を残しているわ　紅く
Has not yet completely vanished
Mada katachi o nokoshiteiru wa
I glimpse a vivid red eternity
Akaku azayaka na eien ga miete
鮮やかな永遠が見えて
It starts singing right next to me
Tonari de sore wa utaidasu
隣でそれは歌いだすわ
What was I born for
ねえ　私を愛して
Come on, love me
Nee watashi o aishite
Because I won't let you go
Hanasanai kara
離さないから
Hello my name is
A world where humans' state of mind
and the tendency of their personalities can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls
are commonly called 'Psycho-Pass.'
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations
that appear in the show are fictitious,
and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.